<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ananke: a Hugo Theme on will的笔记</title>
    <link>/hugo-website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ananke: a Hugo Theme on will的笔记</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/hugo-website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: Quasimodo</title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-7/</guid>
      <description>#科学知识 页岩油，是指以页岩为主的页岩层系中所含的石油资源，其中包括泥页岩孔隙和裂缝中的石油，也包括泥页岩层系中的致密碳酸岩或碎屑岩邻层和夹层中的石油资源。 2017年10月27日，世界卫生组织国际癌症研究机构公布的致癌物清单初步整理参考，页岩油在1类致癌物清单中。 百度百科
页岩油，也称母页岩油或油页岩油，是一种非常规石油（英语：Unconventional oil）。制备方法是加热分解油页岩，加氢或热溶解。这个过程把在岩石中的有机物质转变为合成石油和天然气合成原料。所得的油状物，可以立即作为燃料或用于提供炼油厂。原料的性质可以通过加入氢和除去杂质如硫和氮等来改变。其制成的产品可用于和原油相同的目的。 页岩油- 维基百科</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>ESTONIAN POLITICS EXPLAINED #政治科学
 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hi7wYwlvwS8  爱沙尼亚的民主排名仅比美国低两位 爱沙尼亚的总统（女性）和德国总统差不多，是吉祥物 爱沙尼亚的立法和执行权力主要在议会，101个位置，首相权力有限（首相得听议会的） 三大党（英文是评论区补充）  Keskerakond(Center socialist populist Party但偏左，主要受到非爱沙尼亚本地人支持） Keskrakond who are center-right populists. Used to be lead by arguably the most powerful Estonian politician who was in a lot of scandals, corruption, dirty Russian money etc. Currently at helm by Jüri Ratas, who is a good politician but a more of a &amp;ldquo;ok man&amp;rdquo; if compared to a &amp;ldquo;yes man&amp;rdquo; - trying to moderate his coalition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/hugo-website/post/chapter-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/post/chapter-9/</guid>
      <description>#政治科学
Latin American Studies
1/14 Media Suppression in Mexico: A Conversation with Mexican Journalist Ricardo Raphael 2018年的视频
 墨西哥是叙利亚以外记者最容易死去的地方，去年（？）一年死了三十多个记者，叙利亚则只死了十几个。 墨西哥的言论不自由（新闻不自由)的具体情况，不同的区域不同，有些区域只可以报道事实但不可以分析，有些区域只可以报道某一方的情况，有些区域什么都不可以说。 新闻不自由是由政府的资助（ads）实现的，因为私人企业的广告流向了谷歌脸书这样的地方不再流向传统新闻，传统新闻只能从政府那里得到资金，一旦他们的内容不符合政府要求就会没有钱。政府资助不是透明公开的。 虽然记者钱少又危险但是越来越多的年轻人想当记者，女性也是，现在60%的墨西哥记者是女性。 Q&amp;amp;A：为什么墨西哥是很好的民主政体却还会出现这样的问题？因为local level并不是民主的，是authoritarian的。 Q&amp;amp;A：（只注意了回答）政府支持的传统媒体非常偏向政府，新媒体非常反对政府，没有中间地带。 我的疑问：  被杀的记者中新媒体和传统媒体记者的比例？（既然传统媒体可以直接通过给钱“和平”解决问题）（其实不明白是否有区别因为我们国家的报纸也都有微博） 如果大家都知道传统媒体是假的，那大家为什么还会读它？它为什么没有直接灭亡或者只剩下一家官方报纸？ 外国人接受的是哪方的信息呢？    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/hugo-website/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo-website/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>